Maybe it was God's blessing,
that Xiao Lu, whom I had been longing for,
suddenly appeared before my eyes.
Please.
Let me go.
But I had never seen her like that.
She was skin and bones,
like wild grass that could snap in the wind at any moment.
She didn't recognize me.
But I recognized her at first glance.
Please,
let me go.
I don't want to miss
this only chance to connect with her.
So I spoke up.
Wait.
Do you think
you can get out like this?
Clean up.
I'll take you with me later.
I know she killed Li Ting.
But
I wanted to save her.
Isn't this Zhao?
Zhao,
are you still mad?
Lu.
That was fast.
I avoided the surveillance cameras along the way.
Lu told me what happened to her.
At that moment,
I realized that
in this world,
except for me,
no one could help her.
I figured you would soon discover the dumbwaiter.
Only by gaining weight in a short time
could Lu dispel your suspicions.
The confession is basically true.
Okay.
Officer,
you must not tell Lu
that I was the one who led Li Ting to her.
Even without you,
there would be others.
But because of you,
she at least had some hope,
didn't she?
Officer,
can I see her one more time?
I'm sorry
for dragging you into this.
It's all over.
Let's go.
Lu,
don't give up.
I will wait for you.
You spent half a month
gaining 20 pounds.
It must have been painful.
Compared to the torture over the years,
it's nothing.
I thought getting rid of Li Ting
and being with Dong would be my new life.
But someone like me
probably doesn't deserve happiness.
Someone like you?
What kind of person are you?
If you choose to abandon yourself,
what about those who love you?
Lu Chen.
Although you killed someone,
the judge will consider your long-term domestic violence
and personal safety issues.
They will definitely lighten your sentence.
You are still young.
Rehabilitate well inside.
I believe you will soon regain your freedom.
And Dong Shan said
he is willing to wait for you.
You must cherish
your life.
Officer Zhuang,
Mr. Cheng,
thank you.
Lu Chen,
you said Li Ting forced you into that room.
Then you couldn't possibly know
there was a dumbwaiter in it.
Someone must have taught you how to clean up the traces
and escape the scene.
Can you tell me who that person was?
I don't know who he is.
I only remember that day,
after Li Ting died,
I was very scared.
Suddenly, the phone in the room rang.
The ringing was like a death warrant,
reminding me that this couldn't be kept a secret.
So I decided to answer the phone
and face it calmly.
Hello.
Room service.
It seems Mr. Li is not available.
So the person answering the phone now
must be Ms. Lu Chen.
How do you know?
Since you are able to answer the phone now,
can I assume
that Mr. Li Ting had an accident,
or is he already...
It seems it went smoother than expected.
If so,
I can give you a chance, Ms. Lu.
What chance?
A chance for you to regain your freedom.
I don't need it.
Lu Chen.
I know you want to turn yourself in now,
but as soon as you walk out of that door,
your life will be ruined.
I have a way to get you off the hook.
Trust me.
Do as I say.
First,
get rid of all your traces in the room,
including fingerprints, hair, and blood.
Then turn the AC down to the lowest setting.
Second,
behind the solid wood cabinet in the entryway,
there is an abandoned dumbwaiter.
With your current weight,
you should be able to leave through it.
You asked her why she helped you.
What did she say?
I only remember her saying one thing:
Life is dark,
but the Lighthouse shines forever.
Your hunch was right.
Lighthouse has struck again.
How did they know Lu Chen wanted to kill Li Ting?
It must be a premeditated setup,
turning all chances
into inevitabilities.
Their people must be hiding in the dark,
watching our every move,
to ensure the whole case becomes a dead end.
When Lu Chen left the room,
the dumbwaiter was exposed.
Then someone must have restored the cabinet from the outside.
Liu Ying.
She's the discoverer.
Before we arrived at the scene,
she was the only one who entered the room.
She was the only one with the opportunity to restore the cabinet.
It must be her.
Because she's a cleaner,
it was too easy for her to do all this.
She also provided the time Lu Chen left the hotel.
It really is her.
She is the designer of Lighthouse.
I didn't expect the truth to be like this.
Who would have thought?
To think of such a way to clear suspicion.
Do you think her body can take it?
Amazing.
Captain Zhuang is calling.
Hello, Captain Zhuang.
Find out where Liu Ying lives right away.
She's a major suspect.
Send me the location.
Bring your weapons and meet at Liu Ying's place.
Oh, okay.
I'll go find it now.
Xiaobai.
Slow down.
Captain Zhuang.
Liu Ying's room is on the third floor.
I really didn't expect
it to be her.
Captain Zhuang.
It seems she's been gone for a while.
Hello, Old Shao.
Captain Zhuang.
After Lu Chen confessed,
I immediately took her fingerprints
and the prints left on that half ring,
including Liu Ying's,
and compared them repeatedly.
The final results show
they belong to neither of them.
The fingerprints are neither Lu Chen's
nor Liu Ying's,
right?
This half fingerprint happened to be left in the dumbwaiter.
I just don't understand
why he would do this.